RICHA MISHRA



9468801973 / 6377251742



richamishra56831@gmail.com



https://acesse.one/hVxkd (linkedin)



3071 mishra vihar, 3rd cross bhindo ka rasta, Jaipur, Chandpole bazaar, Jaipur, Rajasthan, 302001.

SUMMARY

A highly passionate individual holding 3 years + experience working with various individual clients and businesses building a base in writing, academic, management for various platform, seeking for an opportunity where I am allowed to use my academia, interpersonal skills, critical analysis, writing skills, and problem-solving skills along with continuous learning and advancing my knowledge towards every topic and to make a positive impact and contribute to the overall goals to be a good citizen towards my country, I am continuously thriving and understanding the markets requirement according to my work, maintaining and creating an effortless system for both litigants. I am trying to make my job a catalyst to weave my personal narrative into broader tapestry of development ensuring that my legacy is one of service, innovation and enduring impact.

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2020 - August 2020

Artist Manager Intern

Jaipur, Rajasthan

Rising Passion Productions

I was assigned to assist, coordinating and scheduling artists appearances, performances, and interviews on the webinars. Help maintain and update artists social media accounts and website Assist with organizing and attending meetings and events related to artist's career Provide administrative support to the production, such as making of the catalog.

January 2021 - April 2022

Sales Head Manager

Jaipur, Rajasthan

Jewellery By Mitali Jain Jaipur, RAJASTHAN

I was assigned with the management of targeted online sales and order fulfillment on shopify, etsy, amazon and various other ecommerce sites to reach the sales targets and managing the e-commerce sales. Offline sales of pop shows, Product listing, inventory management and various content creation /writing for the collections.

April 2022 onwards

Jaipur, Rajasthan

Private tutoring students of class 5-10th and working as freelancer in writing

Took a break from working, and decided to navigate myself towards attempting for UPSC Civil Services Examination for 2 years but found my self unfortunate to clear the examination but it taught me resilience and I discovered my new talent of writing and teaching and using the knowledge that I was gaining while studying I started teaching students as a private tutor and

ghostwriting article and academic research papers and through this I even got a learn a skill of SEO website content writing through a client and now working for those also.

EDUCATION

MAHAVEER PUBLIC SCHOOL, JAIPUR (2004-2016)

- CGPA MARKS 10^{TH} : 7.5 (PASSED IN 2014)
- 12TH PERCENTILE: 67.8 (PASSED IN 2016) with commerce and applied arts.

ST. XAVIERS COLLEGE, JAIPUR

- M.A. Economics (2019-2021) secured first division.
- B.A. Economics (2016-2019) secured second division 57.8%.

SKILLS

- MS Word
- Ms Excel
- Management
- Creative Content Writing
- Academic Content Writing
- Canva
- Photoshop (beginner)
- Tally
- E- Commerce management (not advanced still upgrading skills)
- Inventory management
- Eway bills management
- Shopify handling expert
- Email management

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Achieved and A Grade in college student development program
- Got 2 of my research paper published in journal of my college which is now a national journals
- Head Editor for economics department research journal
- Organizing Head for cultural Committee

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Crafting in clay sculptures and pottery
- painting